(Penny:)Question one.
"Given the choice
"of anyone in the world,
whom would you want
as a dinner guest?"
(Leonard:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)Living or dead?
Just says "anyone in the world."
(Penny:)I guess that means living.
(Sheldon:)Ah, that's just as well.
(Sheldon:)As much as I'd love
to meet Euclid--
(Sheldon:)inventor of the
geometric proof--
(Sheldon:)he probably wore
sandals and I cannot
(Sheldon:)look at toes during dinner.
Oh, I know!
(Sheldon:)The person I'd most
like to have dinner with
(Sheldon:)is myself.
(Penny:)You sure that's your choice?
'Cause I've had that dinner.
(Sheldon:)Well, I haven't.
(Sheldon:)And while they say
never meet your heroes,
(Sheldon:)I just don't see how
I could disappoint.
(Sheldon:)Who would you choose?
(Penny:)Robert Downey, Jr.
You...
Oh!
(Sheldon:)I didn't think of Iron Man.
(Sheldon:)You know, maybe after
myself and I have dinner,
(Sheldon:)we can meet you two for dessert.
(Raj:)So, what do you
guys want to do?
(Amy:)Well, we're the ones
tagging along, you pick.